<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Learn Android Studio 3</title>
    <link>http://tedhagos.com/learnandroidstudio3/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Learn Android Studio 3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 12:03:47 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tedhagos.com/learnandroidstudio3/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Handling</title>
      <link>http://tedhagos.com/learnandroidstudio3/posts/event-handling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 12:03:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tedhagos.com/learnandroidstudio3/posts/event-handling/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://tedhagos.com/learnandroidstudio3/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 17:36:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tedhagos.com/learnandroidstudio3/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>Build Android apps using the popular and efficient Android Studio 3 suite of tools, an integrated development environment (IDE) with which Android developers can now use the Kotlin programming language. With this book, you’ll learn the latest and most productive tools in the Android tools ecosystem, ensuring quick Android app development and minimal effort on your part. Along the way, you’ll use Android Studio to develop apps tier by tier through practical examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How it began</title>
      <link>http://tedhagos.com/learnandroidstudio3/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 12:03:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tedhagos.com/learnandroidstudio3/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>Sometime in 2010, I picked up Android. I&amp;rsquo;ve had more than 10 years of Java experience at that point, so I thought it wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be a big deal. I was wrong — writing programs for Android was very different from writing programs for the web and desktop 2013, I held some seminars and workshops on the subject 2015, I started writing Minimum Android Programming on LeanPub. A couple of folks bought it, even if it wasn&amp;rsquo;t finished yet Valentines day of 2017, I got an email from Apress, they wanted me to revise &amp;ldquo;Learn Android Studio&amp;rdquo; July 2017, Finalizing the instructional design August 2017, signed the contract for 2 books 3rd quarter 2017, I began writing Learn Android Studio 3 (Java ed) Nov 2017, I&amp;rsquo;m not nearly half-finished.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>